Guide to the Jesse Simons Papers WAG.044
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series II: Arbitration Decisions, undated
  - Freeport Teachers' Association v. Board of Education Union Free School District No. 9, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - General Warehousemen's Union, Local 852 v. Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. (3 cases), undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - General Warehousemen's Union, Local 853 v. Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co., undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Gutkin, Morton, Dr. v. Kings Highway Medical Group, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Hallpike, Violet (Civil Service Employees Association, CSEA) v. NY State Department of Mental Hygiene, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Hastings-on-Hudson Teachers' Association v. Hastings-on-Hudson Board of Education, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Heisman, Saul (Deceased), Estate of v. Health and Welfare Fund, Local 338, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees (HERE), Local 100 v. Andrea Consultants, Ltd., undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - HERE, Local 100 v. Service International Corp., undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - HERE, Local 100 v. Farney's Restaurant, Inc., undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - HERE, Local 100 v. Museum of Modern Art, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, Local 76 v. S. and H. Grossinger, Inc., undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home and Allied Health Services Union, Local 144 v. Jamaica Hospital, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home and Allied Health Services Union, Local 144 v. Massapequa General Hospital, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Hudson County Newspaper Pressman's Union v. Evening Journal Association, undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Hyman, Abraham v. US Department of Labor, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Independent Association of Publishers' Employees (IAPE) v. Wall Street Journal, undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Independent Federation of Flight Attendants v. Trans World Airlines (7 cases), undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Independent Union of Flight Attendants v. Pan-American World Airways, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Independent Workers of North America, Local 429 v. Blue Circle Atlantic, Inc., undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Insurance Workers International Union v. Metropolitan Life Insurance (2 cases), undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees Union (IATSE), Local 771 v. American Broadcasting Company (ABC), undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - IATSE, Local 771 v. National Broadcasting Company (NBC), undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - IATSE, Local 306 v. Museum of Modern Art, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - IATSE and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the US and Canada, Local 306 v. WPIX, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Local 455 v. Dayton Metal Products, undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Local 455 v. Fabricator's Steel Corp., undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - International Association of Machinists, Local 571 v. A.M. Varityper, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - International Association of Machinists v. Autosplice, Inc., undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - International Association of Machinists, Lodge 703 v. Curtiss-Wright Corp. (4 cases), undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - International Association of Machinists, Lodge 354 v. Dunham-Bush, Inc., undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - International Association of Machinists v. Ellwood Manufacturing, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - International Association of Machinists v. F.M. Schaefer Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - International Association of Machinists, Local 447 v. Hertz Corp. (2 cases), undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - International Association of Machinists, Local 2130 v. Hoke, Inc. (2 cases), undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - International Association of Machinists, D.C. 15 v. Lockheed Aircraft, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - International Association of Machinists, Local 2587 v. Miller Brewing Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - International Association of Machinists v. Newark Morning Ledger, Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - International Association of Machinists, D.C. 15 v. Raritan Periodical Sales, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - International Association of Machinists, Local 402 v. Republic Steel Corp. (2 cases), undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - International Association of Machinists v. Ryder Truck Rental, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - International Association of Machinists v. Silent House and Crane Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - International Association of Machinists v. Teledyne Farris Engineering, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - International Association of Machinists, Local 447 v. United Parcel Service Co. (12 cases), undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers v. Curtiss-Wright Corp., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers v. Howe Richardson Scale Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers v. Northwest Airlines Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers v. R.E.A. Express Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 447 v. United Postal Service (3 cases), undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Local 1164 v. General Cable Corp., undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - IBEW, Local 3 v. GTE Telenet Information Services, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - IBEW, Local 503 v. Highland Telephone Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - IBEW, Local 3 v. Holmes Protection, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - IBEW, Local 2154 v. National Fuel Gas Co. (3 cases), undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - IBEW v. New England Telephone and Telegraph Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - IBEW, Local 2222 v. New England Telephone and Telegraph Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - IBEW, Local 2320 v. New England Telephone and Telegraph Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - IBEW, Local 2322 v. New England Telephone and Telegraph Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - IBEW, Local 2323 v. New England Telephone and Telegraph Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - IBEW, Locals 2222, 2313, 2315, and 2320-27 v. New England Telephone and Telegraph Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - IBEW, Locals 2222, 2315, 2320-27 v. New England Telephone and Telegraph Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - IBEW, Locals 2222, 2320, 2323, 2324, 2326, 2327 v. New England Telephone and Telegraph Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - IBEW, Locals 2222, 2313, 2320, 2321, 2322, 2323, 2324, 2325, 2326, and 2327 v. New England Telephone and Telegraph Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - IBEW, Local 2213 v. New York Telephone Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - IBEW, Local 503 v. Orange and Rockland Utilities, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - IBEW, Local 3 v. Publisher's Association of New York City, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - IBEW, Local 455 v. Western Massachusetts Electric Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - International Brotherhood of Electricians, Local 2213 v. New York Telephone Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, L. 31190 v. United Health Services Wilson Hospital, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - International Brotherhood of Pulp Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 387 v. Georgia-Pacific Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - International Brotherhood of Pulp Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 413 v. Holsom Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 229 v. Affiliated Food Distributors (2 cases), undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - IBT, Local 868 v. ASPCA (2 cases), undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - IBT, Local 917, v. Bush Terminal Associates, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - IBT, Local 175 v. Chemical Leaman Tank Lines, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - IBT, Local 237 v. CUNY (2 cases), undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - IBT, Local 170 v. Consolidated Beverages, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - IBT, Local 282 v. Glover Bottled Gas Corp., undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - IBT, Local 810 v. Greenwald Industries, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - IBT, Local 46 v. Guinness-Harp Corp., undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - IBT, Local 229 v. Harper and Collins, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - IBT, Local 917 v. Hartz Mountain Corp., undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - IBT, Local 854 v. Hudson River Aggregates, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - IBT, Local 237 v. Jacob Javits Convention Center, undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - IBT, Local 917 v. Kinney Systems, undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - IBT, Local 803 v. Main Security Service, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - IBT, Local 868 v. NY Twist Drill, undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - IBT, Local 97 v. Panelgraphic Corp., undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - IBT, Local 810 v. Phelps Memorial Hospital, undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - IBT, Local 46 v. Preferred Distributing Corp., undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - IBT, Local 56 v. Rheingold Breweries, Inc., undated (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - IBT, Local 210 v. Security Furniture Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - IBT, Local 814 v. Sotheby's, undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - IBT, Local 229 v. Supermarket Service Corp. (2 cases), undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - IBT, Local 169 v. Transco Service Corp., undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - IBT, Local 97 v. Twin Oaks Nursing Home, undated (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - IBT, Local 177 v. UPS (6 cases), undated (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - IBT, Local 623 v. UPS, undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - IBT, Local 804 v. UPS (8 cases), undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - IBT, Local 282 v. Warshaw, Inc., undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - IBT, Local 813 v. Waste Management of NY, undated (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - International Chemical Workers Union, Local 111 v. American Cyanamid Co., undated (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - International Chemical Workers Union, Local 677 v. Kay-Fries Chemicals, undated (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - International Chemical Workers Union, Local 143 v. Lederle Laboratories, undated (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Unions (ILGWU), Local 160 v. Maidenform, Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - ILGWU v. Mid-Atlantic Textile Co., undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - ILGWU, Local 23/25 v. Pauline Originals, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - International Leather Goods, Plastics, and Novelty Workers Union v. Harklo Handbag Corp., undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - International Leather Goods, Plastics, and Novelty Workers Union v. Legendary Leather Accessories, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - International Longshoremen's Association, Local 1814 v. Amstar Sugar Corp., undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - ILA, United Marine Division, Local 333 v. Marine Towing and Transportation Employer's Association, undated (Box 7, Folder 6a)
  - International Molders and Allied Workers Union v. Chapman Division, Crane Co., undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - International Production Service and Sales Employees Union, Local 719 v. Camp Laboratories, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - International Production Service and Sales Employees Union, Local 300 v. Charm Craft Publishers, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Technical, Salaries and Machine Workers, Local 496 v. AKZO Chemicals, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, Local 431 v. A.E. Electronics, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 463 v. Amperex Electronics, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 463 v. Ideal Corp., undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 475 v. Teledyne Hydra Power Co., undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers (IUE), Local 458 v. Arrow Lock Company, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - International Union of Elevator Constructors, Local 1 v. General Elevator Co., undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - International Union of Elevator Constructors, Local 1 v. Otis Elevator Co. (2 cases), undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - International Union of Elevator Constructors, Local 1 v. Otis Elevator Co. v. VTM Elevator Co., undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 30 v. Madison Square Garden, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 94-94A-94B v. Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 30 v. Safe Affordable Housing for Everyone, Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Kluglein, Mary Patricia v. Shaw, Hollis (Wassaic Developmental Disabilities Services Office), undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Kluglein, Mary Patricia v. Simons, Jesse (1 of 2), undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Kluglein, Mary Patricia v. Simons, Jesse (2 of 2), undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Larchmont-Mamaronek Non-Teaching Unit, CSEA, Inc., and AFSCME Local 1000 v. Mamaronek Union Free School District, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Lifeguard Supervisor's Union, Local 508 v. City of New York, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Loews Glenpointe Hotel v. Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE), Local 69, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Marine Engineers Beneficial Association v. Central Railroad Co. of NJ, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Metal Trades Council of New London County v. General Dynamics Corp. (2 cases), undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Metro-North Commuter Railroad v. Railroad Police Benevolent Association, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Meyers Parking System v. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 917, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Monagahela Valley Typographical Union, Local 504 v. The Valley Independent, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Moore McCormack Bulk Transport v. National Maritime Union, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - National City Printing Pressmen and Assistants Union, Local 406 v. Newsday (4 cases), undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians (NABET) v. National Broadcasting Co. (NBC), undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - National Association of Letter Carriers v. USPS (17 cases), undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - National Council Distributive Workers of America, District #65 v. Direct Mail Contract Association (4 cases), undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - National Council Distributive Workers of America, District #65 v. Direct Mail Severance Fund, Trustees, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - National Council Distributive Workers of America, District #65 v. Public Service Letter and Printing Co., undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - National Council Distributive Workers of America, District #65 v. Speed-O-Lite Offset Corp., undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - National Council of EEOC, Local 216 and American Federation of Government Employees, Local 35 v. U.S. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - National Maritime Union v. Afram Lines Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - National Maritime Union v. American Marine Lines, undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - National Maritime Union v. Atlantic Marine Agencies, undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - National Maritime Union v. Farrell Lines, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - National Maritime Union v. Gulf Refining Co., undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - National Maritime Union v. Keystone Shipping Co. (3 cases), undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - National Maritime Union v. Marine Transport Lines (3 cases), undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - National Maritime Union v. Moore-McCormack Lines, undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - National Maritime Union v. Prudential Lines, undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - National Maritime Union v. Sigma Ship Agency, undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - National Maritime Union v. Texaco, undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - National Maritime Union v. Texaco Maritime Services, undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - National Maritime Union v. U.S. Lines (7 cases), undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - National Maritime Union, Unlicensed Division v. Puerto Rico Marine Management, undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - National Maritime Union, Unlicensed Division v. Tanker Service Committee (2 cases), undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - National Maritime Union, Unlicensed Division v. Texaco Marine Services, undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - National Union of Hospital and Healthcare Employees, District #1199 v. Brooklyn Cumberland Medical Center, undated (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - National Union of Hospital and Healthcare Employees, District #1199 v. League of voluntary Hospitals, undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - National Union of Hospital and Healthcare Employees v. Mt. Sinai Hospital, undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - National Union of Hospital and Healthcare Employees, District #1191 v. New York University Medical Center, undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - National Union of Hospital and Healthcare Employees, District #1199 v. Presbyterian Hospital, undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - National Union of Hospital and Healthcare Employees, District #1199 v. Yeshiva University, undated (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees, District #1199 v., undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - New York City Health and Hospitals Corp. v. American State, County, and Municipal Workers Union, District Council #37, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - New York City School Construction Authority v. Civil Service Technical Guild, Local 375, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - New York News v. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, D.C. 15, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - New York Printing Pressman's Union v. New York Times Co., undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - New York Professional Nurses Union v. Lennox Hill Hospital, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - New York Convention Operating Co. v. City Employees Union, Local 237, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - New York State Nurses Association (NYSNA) v. Cabrini Medical Center (4 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - NYSNA v. Central General Hospital, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - NYSNA v. Community General Hospital of Sullivan City (2 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - NYSNA v. Gloversville Extended Care and Nursing Home, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - NYSNA v. Gracie Square Hospital (4 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - NYSNA v. Greene County Public Health Nursing home, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - NYSNA v. Horton Memorial Hospital, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - NYSNA v. Ingersoll Nursing Home, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - NYSNA v. Interboro General Hospital (3 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - NYSNA v. Interfaith Medical Center, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - NYSNA v. Jewish Hospital and Medical Center, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - NYSNA v. Jewish Institute for Geriatric Care, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - NYSNA v. Kingsbrook Jewish Medical Center (5 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - NYSNA v. Maimonides Medical Center (10 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - NYSNA v. Mary Immaculate Hospital (3 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - NYSNA v. Metropolitan NY Nursing Home Association, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - NYSNA v. Mid-Island Hospital (2 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - NYSNA v. Montefiore Hospital and Medical Center, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - NYSNA v. Mt. Sinai Hospital (2 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - NYSNA v. Mount Vernon Hospital (3 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - NYSNA v. Nathan Littauer Hospital Association, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - NYSNA v. Nyack Hospital, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - NYSNA v. Pelham Bay General Hospital, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - NYSNA v. Peninsula Hospital Center, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - NYSNA v. Presbyterian Hospital (21 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - NYSNA v. Roosevelt Hospital (2 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - NYSNA v. St. John's Episcopal Hospital of Brooklyn, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - NYSNA v. St. Luke's Hospital, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - NYSNA v. St. Luke's - Roosevelt Hospital Center (2 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - NYSNA v. St. Vincent's Hospital, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - NYSNA v. Tremont Community Council Vocational Instruction Project, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - NYSNA v. Unity Hospital, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - NYSNA v. Westchester County Medical Center (2 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - NYSNA v. Westchester Square Hospital, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - NYSNA v. Wyckoff Heights Hospital (2 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - New York State Permanent Firemen's Association v. City of Plattsburgh, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - New York State United Teachers v. Locust Valley Central School District Board of Education, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - New York State United Teachers v. Pearl River Board of Education, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - New York Telephone Co. v. CWA, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - New York Times v. New York Mailers' Union #6 (2 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - New York Typographical Union, #6 v. Gazette Press, undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - New York Typographical Union, #6 v. Long Island Press, undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - New York Typographical Union, #6 v. New York News, undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Newark Newspaper Printing Pressman's Union v. Newark Morning Ledger (2 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Newspaper Guild of Buffalo, Local 26 v. Tonawanda Publishing, undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3 v. Consumers' Union of U.S., undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3 v. New York News (2 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3 v. Reuters Ltd., undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York v. Time Inc. (2 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York v. Crescent News Distributors, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union v. Daily News v. Weinberg News Co., undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York v. Jesse Simons v. Daily Racing Form, Inc., undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union v. New Brunswick Newsdealers Supply Co., undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of NY v. NY News, undated (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union (NMDU) v. Newark Star Ledger (3 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - North Jersey Newspaper Guild, Local 173 v. Alco-Gravure, Inc., undated (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 153 v. AFSCME, D.C. #37, undated (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - OPEIU v. Dart Container Lines, Inc., undated (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - OPEIU, Local 153 v. Depository Trust Co. (2 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - OPEIU, Local 402 v. Puerto Rico Marine Management Inc., undated (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Union (OCAW), Local 8-166 v. Allied Signal, Inc., undated (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - OCAW, Local 8-956 v. BASF Corp., undated (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - OCAW, Local 8-12058 v. Carborundum Co. (2 cases), undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - OCAW, Local 8-138 v. E.R. Squibb and Sons, Inc., undated (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - OCAW, Local 8-490 v. Standard Oil Co., undated (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - OCAW, Local 8-623 v. Texaco Inc., undated (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Paint, Chemical, Clerical, Warehouse and Industrial Union, Local 1310 v. Essex Chemical Corp., undated (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Paint, Chemical, Clerical, Warehouse and Industrial Union, Local 1310 v. Toledo Scale, undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Paper Handlers' and Sheet Straighteners' Union, #1 v. American Bank Note Co., undated (Box 8, Folder 75)